So in a previous video we did an analysis where we looked at
所以，在之前的视频中，我们做了一个分析，我们看到了
what countries do our most popular beers stem from?
我们最受欢迎的啤酒是来自于哪些国家的？
But of course if we're talking about geographical data
不过，当然，如果我们谈论的是 地理数据
like countries, maybe we could plot that on a map.
例如国家，也许我们可以把这些数据绘制到地图上。
And in our worksheet we also have information
而在我们的工作表上我们也有
about latitude and longitude, so wouldn't it be cool if we would have a map of the world
有关纬度和经度的信息，因此若我们用一幅世界地图显示我们最受欢迎的啤酒的
that would show exactly where the breweries are where our most popular beers come from.
啤酒厂的准确位置， 那岂不是更加完美。
Maybe we can plan a field trip to the closest most popular brewery.
也许我们可以安排离我们最近的最受欢迎啤酒厂的实地考察。
so luckily there's a super cool thing in Excel 2013 that's called
幸运的是 Excel 2013有个很酷的东西，
PowerMap. We're going to use that to do exactly that, plot
它就叫做POWERMAP。 我们将用它来
our beers on a map. So you just
在地图上标绘啤酒。 所以当你 安装了这个插件，
click power map when you have installed this plug-in,
你只要点击POWERMAP，
and then you get a map right there and all the data
然后您会在那里获得一概览图, 而
from our data model from PowerPivot is right there.
所有来自PowerPiovt的数据模型中的数据就在那里。
So what we can do is drag just the breweries on and
所以我们能够做的就是, 拖住"啤酒厂"
you get  little dots for all of the breweries. But this is based on the entire
所有的"啤酒厂"上就会出现小点。 但是这是基于整个
list of breweries,
啤酒厂列表，
on the one worksheet. Not yet on the connected list
在一个工作表上的 。 还不在
connected to what we are selling. In order for us to do that,
与我们销售所相连的连接列表。 若我们要那样做，
we need to drag the quantity in, very similar to how we would do it in a
我们需要把"数量"拖动进来， 类似于我们
normal pivot table.
在操作常规数据透视表那样 。
And what we get then is all the brewery with the quantity that we
然后便列出所有的"啤酒厂", 连同
are selling in our bar so we can see that this
它们在我们酒吧所卖啤酒的数目，那么, 我们可以看到
brewery right here this is the La Trappe brewery is kinda close to where our bar is.
这里所列的啤酒厂，是邻近我们的酒吧的La Trappe啤酒厂。
Let's assume our bar is in Delft, where this university is too.
假设我们的酒吧和这大学都位于代尔夫特 。
So we have a pretty popular brewery that is quite close
而我们有一相当流行的啤酒厂
to Delft, that would be nice for a field trip. So what I've done now is, I have also added the
其厂址十分邻近代尔夫特，那么实地考察未尝不可。 所以，我现在所做的是，我还添加了
time
"时间"这一项
dimension and you get a little animation where you can see
您会看到一小动态画面, 当中显示
during that time, during the opening hours of our bar
在这那段时间里，在我们酒吧营业时间内
you see the beers basically being drunk by the people
您可看到酒吧里客人所消费的啤酒品种和数目
in the bar and you can play that time as an animation.
您可以把这段时间以动画的形式展示。
What we can furthermore do, is add a category so you see what type of beers
我们还可以，添加一分类, 然后您便可以看到不同类别的啤酒
stem from what brewery. So you see here
源自哪些啤酒厂。 那么, 你看看这里
let me remove that, you see that blue is a certain type of beer,
让我删除这项，你看, 那蓝色的 代表某种啤酒，
and orange is not our type of beer and you see a right on your map.
橙色的不是我们的啤酒类别， 您可在概览图中看到。
No formulas needed. You just drag your data in, you say
不需要使用公式。 只需把数据拖进来， 你说
these are the breweries, the quantities and the categories
这些都是啤酒厂， 啤酒数量和种类
and you get your visualisation right on the map. So let's have a look at the
然后你便在概览图中看到所有信息。 那么，让我们来看看
rest of the world we don't need to concentrate on Europe. If you look at the
世界其他地方，我们并不需要 只针对欧洲地区。 如果你看
US we see another interesting
美国，我们会看到另一个有趣的
visualization, we see that here the breweries of which
可视化图像信息，我们看到，这里的酿酒厂
two of the beers that are being sold are really popular and here's an
(出售其中两种啤酒)很受欢迎，这里是另一个
area in the US where a lot of breweries are popular.
在美国的地区，该地区有不少受消费者青睐的啤酒厂。
So maybe if we want to have a field trip very far away
因此，如果我们希望到远地进行实地考察
this would be an interesting area of the US to actually go to.
这个地区实际上是个不错的选择。
And again and I can't stress this enough we didn't use
再者, 我郑重强调，我们 并没有使用
any formulas if we just load all our data into the PowerPivot data model
任何公式。我们只是把所有数据加载到PowerPivot数据模型当中
we can then use PowerMap if it's geographical data
如果涉及地理数据, 我们就可以使用POWERMAP
to plot everything on a map just by selecting the fields
只需要选择"区域", 便可以在概览图上编制所有
that we want to use. And that closes the entire week
我们希望使用的信息。 而那结束了整个星期
to show you the power of pivot tables little use of formulas, you can just
向你展示数据透视表的强大功能, 几乎不需要使用公式，您可以仅仅
analyze your data by clicking and dragging
通过点击拖动操作完成分析数据
isn't that nice? See you next week
这不是很棒么？ 下周见